

NICOLÁS CAGIAO

Age: 34 – Argentinian +54 9 (011) 15-6017-0178 +54 9 (011) 15-<u>3818</u>-1470 Ciudad Autónoma de Buenos Aires nico.cagiao@gmail.com nicolascagiao.com

ABOUT ME

I have knowledge in **HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, MySql, PHP**, I'm a Community Manager, and was a senior editor and writer for 6 years in <u>DiarioSobreDiarios.com</u> (currently off-line). At the time, my actual job consists in auditing media for <u>Ejes de Comunicación</u>.

I have an upper/intermediate English level and I recently finished 2 programming courses at the Universidad Tecnológica Nacional of Buenos Aires (<u>UTN</u>).

PERSONAL OBJECTIVE

Im a hard-working junior level programmer focused on **learning new ways to solve problems**. I believe programming is THE path to achieve more efficiency and quality of data management. I have great **soft skills** and I work better in teams.

Availability: Full Time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Daw Análisis y Comunicación – (2018 - currently)Newspaper auditing plus private and public report writing.

Ejes de Comunicación / Ejes / www.ejes.com – (2016 - currently) Tv and radio auditing.

Diario sobre Diarios / Grupo Consenso S.A. / eldsd.com - (2013 - currently) Senior editor and writer for 6 years, Community Manager tasks.

Mevaterapia S.A. Medical center / Administrative – Capital Federal. **(2008 – 2014)** Almost six years of administrative tasks, including public customer support

EDUCATION

Online Courses: "Cómo programar para emprendedores" (Javascript) course & Modern Javascript for beginners course (Udemy). – (2020)

Fullstack Programming course (JavaScript & JS Frameworks (Angular JS, React), Mercado Pago) – (2019)

Professional Webmaster course - Web Markup (HTML5 & CSS3). Responsive design y web layout. PHP Y MYSQL. UX/UI. FLEXBOX. – **(2019)**

Communication course – Universidad Popular de las Madres de Plaza de Mayo – Capital Federal (2015 - incomplete). – **(2015)**

Community Management - University of Buenos Aires - Capital Federal (CAPACITARTE) - (2015)

Politic journalism course with Mario Wainfeld - Anfibia Magazine (20hs.) - (2015)

Basic photography – Photography workshop SEU/FADU/ University of Buenos Aires (http://www.fadu.uba.ar/) – (2014)

Investigative Journalism – Universidad popular de las Madres de Plaza de Mayo – Capital Federal (one year) – **(2013)**

Photojournalism – Photographers cooperative Sub (<u>Sub</u>) – (2013)

Medicine - Universidad de Buenos Aires - Incomplete - (2005)

High School degree on economics of enterprises and organizations. "Comercial Mixto Juan XXIII" institute - Carlos Casares. – **(2004)**

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Github, Visual Studio Code, Sublime
- Discord, Slack, Trello
- Office, Design, audio and video editing.
- Wordpress, Photoshop, Premiere, Lightroom
- Upper/intermediate English level
- Photography and Journalism
- Community Manager.

LANGUAGES

FIRST CERTIFICATE IN ENGLISH (ESOL), UNIVERSITY OF CAMBRIDGE. Awarded Grade B. - (2004)

Complete full superior course of English at the Paddington English Institute/Carlos Casares. – (1998 - 2003)

Russian language course at the "Casa de Rusia" / Ciudad de Buenos Aires - 6 Months. - (2018)

PROYECTS

Online Newspaper with the possibility to publish stories https://nuevodsd.000webhostapp.com/index.php -HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, PHP, MYSQL (all from scratch). Ajax for the Contact Form. **Work in progress**.

References:

Diario sobre Diarios – Grupo Consenso S.A - Dardo A. Fernández +54 9 (011) - 4362-5849

Ejes de Comunicación – Alem 1110 7° Piso. - CABA - Tel +54 9 (011) 5352-0550 rrhh@ejes.com

Centro Médico Mevaterapia S.A. – Noelia Sulak +54 9 (011) – 4958-1213 – +54 9 (011)-15-31784750